ABHISHEK JH

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bonito Designs Aug 2022 - Present

GRAPHIC DESIGNER
 Interior design
 www.bonito.in

K12 Techno Services Pvt. Ltd Jun 2019 - Aug 2022

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Education Service Provider k12technoservices.com

Travtech Software Pvt Ltd May 2017- May 2019 GRAPHIC DESIGNER
 Cruisebase Company www.travtech.com

EDUCATION

WEB & GRAPHIC DESIGNING COURSE

2016

Image Creative Education Jayanagar, Bangalore - 560011

DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE 2011-2015

Govt Polytechnic. Belur - 577101

PUC 2009-2011

Govt PU College Chikmagaluru - 577101

SSLC 2009 Vishwa-Vidyalaya High School. Chikmagaluru - 577101

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

• • • • • •

ADOBE IN-DESIGN

• • • • • • •

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

ADOBE PREMIERE PRO

• • • • • • •

ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS

• • • • • • •

FIGMA

WORDPRESS

ABOUT ME

Innovative Graphic Designing with 6 years of extensive design experience across high-profile projects. Works with drive and care to conceptualize and create client briefs within deadlines. Committed to maintaining high standards for excellent customer satisfaction.

CONTACT

- NSR Layout, Bangalore-560102
- (+91) 9353035219
- jhabhishek7@gmail.com

PERMANENT ADDRESS

\$\ s\\$ o Haleshappa R
Agrahara circle,
Kote,
Chikmagaluru,
Karnataka
Pin:-577101

Highly creative and multitalented Graphic Designer with extensive experience in multimedia, marketing and print design.

Creative experience in the following:

PRINT

- Brochures & Newsletters
- Logos & Business Cards
- Posters & Post Cards
- Flyers
- Catalogue
- Banners
- Packaging Design

WEB & MULTIMEDIA

- Social Media Post
- UI/UX Design
- Video Editing
- HTML/CSS

1. Travtech Software Pvt Ltd

- Junior Graphic Designer
 - * Brochure Designing
 - * html/css
 - Creating/Updating Webpages.

* Image editing

2. K12 Techno Service Pvt. Ltd

- Graphic Designer
 - * Newsletters
 - * Magazines
 - * Kid's Textbook
 - * Packaging Designing
- * Posters
- * Printing Designing
- * Activities book
- * Social media Creatives

3. Bonito Desigs

- Graphic Designer
 - * Trendbooks
 - * Social media creatives
 - * Youtube video editing
 - * UI/UX Designing
- * Marketing & Digital Ads creatives
- * Motion graphics
- * Brand Creatives
- * Wordpress Updating content

Portfolio link: https://drive.google.com/drive/u/1/folders/1oxUv7kiQqkwTQayErk7s32myDNqV2mBq

PLACE: BANGALORE SIGNATURE

DATE: (ABHISHEK JH)